<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on permission trip</title>
    <link>https://graysonhary.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on permission trip</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 21:02:51 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://graysonhary.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Grandma</title>
      <link>https://graysonhary.com/posts/2023-12-30-grandma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 21:02:51 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://graysonhary.com/posts/2023-12-30-grandma/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had Covid for the last week. My last day before isolating was on December 22, a Friday, when I took the day off to visit my Grandma, Shirley, in hospice in St. Cloud, MN. A few weeks earlier, my folks, my sister, and myself had visited her, during the first full day she was in hospice, and she was doing well, in high spirits, but we knew her condition may worsen at any moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Happening</title>
      <link>https://graysonhary.com/posts/08-12-2023-whats-happening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 23:08:30 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://graysonhary.com/posts/08-12-2023-whats-happening/</guid>
      <description>Chugging along with this blog! It&amp;rsquo;s not yet published to the web but I am adding entries to it as I work on styling it.
Cafe Allez. Chicago, IL. November 2023. Aesop Bucktown. Chicago, IL. November 2023. Mildblend. November 2023. AnnMarie and I at Independence. November 2023. AnnMarie. Chicago, IL. November 2023. AnnMarie and John. Chicago, IL. November 2023. AnnMarie and Olivia. Chicago, IL. November 2023. AnnMarie and Olivia. Chicago, IL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something New</title>
      <link>https://graysonhary.com/posts/28-11-2023-something-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:19:55 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://graysonhary.com/posts/28-11-2023-something-new/</guid>
      <description>Howdy
I mentioned to a friend and his new partner late last year that I had been considering starting a new blog to share whatever was on my mind, primarily photos and the like. Now that a year has passed, I think it’s time to get something off the ground with this.
Harmony Coffee in Minneapolis. November 2023. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
